<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">

    <string name="app_name">Brevent</string>

    <string name="fragment_guide_welcome">Bienvenue</string>
    <string name="fragment_guide_welcome_message">Comment quittez-vous les applis ?\nQuand vous avez fini votre travail et voulez la quitter, vous appuyez sur le bouton Retour.\nSi vous appuyez sur le bouton Accueil, l'appli se fait rendue à l'arrière-plan et l'appli Launcher démarre.</string>
    <string name="fragment_guide_welcome_message2">Ce style d'Android nous plaît, mais il y a des applis que le détestent. Elles se cachent à l'arrière-plan et consomment votre batterie, dont les applis vous ennuient en vous envoyant les Notification push inutiles.\n\nMaintenant, voici Brevent qui protége votre appareil pour vous de ces applis.\nQuand une appli est glissée hors de l'écran Applis recentes ou vous voulez la terminez en annuyant le Retour, elle est forcée à se terminer.\nAppuyer sur l'Accueil ne la permet d'aller à l'arrière-plan pour finir son travail qu'avant le time-out defini par vous n'arrive.\n\nBrevent affiche le temps inactif pour chaque applis dans l'arrière-plan.</string>

    <string name="fragment_guide_permission">Permissions</string>
    <string name="fragment_guide_permission_message">What do you need to do? \nJust a simple command with your PC.</string>
    <string name="fragment_guide_permission_message2">Some similar apps require root access or modifying your unlocked device. Debugging mode doesn\'t require root access, nor unlocking, it\'s much safer to use. \n\nThere is an experimental ROOT feature, allowing you to skip turning on debugging mode, even starting Brevent service when completed booting. You can press Back 7 times on \"Please start Brevent service\" page, or press \"Version\" 7 times in \"Settings\". ROOT mode is unsafe and unnessary, we do not offer support for those who prefer ROOT mode.</string>

    <string name="fragment_guide_security">Security</string>
    <string name="fragment_guide_security_message">We need debugging mode to launch our Brevent without rooting your device. However, debugging mode is not safe enough, we strongly recommend you turn it off after starting Brevent service successfully.</string>
    <string name="fragment_guide_security_message2">Brevent uses plenty of Android\'s hidden APIs. Some third-party ROMs may modify these API, so there would be some issues when using.</string>

    <string name="fragment_guide_enjoy">Enjoy</string>
    <string name="fragment_guide_enjoy_message">Enjoy Brevent, and feel free to feedback.</string>
    <string name="fragment_guide_enjoy_message2">The default Brevent method is \"App Standby\"(since Android 6.0). If you find some apps still running, please use Brevent or other tools to check its status.\n\nAnd to increase battery performance, Brevent server delay the processes by 3 to 60 seconds according the event level.\n\nWhen you swipe apps away from recent screen, Android will kill the processes and Brevent would force-stop them ASAP.</string>

    <string name="fragment_guide_adb">ADB</string>
    <string name="fragment_guide_adb_message">ADB (Android Debug Bridge) is a command-line tool that lets you communicate with an Android device. It\'s part of platform-tools, you can download it from here: https://developer.android.com/studio/releases/platform-tools.html (Long press, then select and copy).</string>
    <string name="fragment_guide_adb_message2">1. uncompress platform-tools-latest-&lt;platform&gt;.zip\n\n2. navigate to platform-tools directory\n\n3. (for Windows) Hold Shift key, then right-click, choose \"Open command window here\", you can run \"adb\" now\n\n3. (for Mac OS X) Navigate \"Finder\", \"Applications\", \"Utilities\", open \"Terminal\", then drag \"adb\" into the \"Terminal\" (please remove duplicate \"adb\" when paste the command line)</string>

    <string name="start_brevent">Start Brevent</string>

    <string name="brevent_service_start">Please start Brevent service</string>
    <string name="brevent_service_restart">Please restart Brevent Service</string>
    <string name="brevent_service_guide">1. Turn on \"Developer options\", enable \"USB debugging\" %1$s\n\n2. Connect to PC via USB %2$s\n\n3. Execute in PC\'s command line \"adb devices\", make sure PC can find device (Reader \"Guide - ADB\")\n\n4. Execute in PC\'s command line \"%3$s\"</string>
    <string name="brevent_service_open_development">Developer options</string>
    <string name="brevent_service_copy_path">Copy command</string>
    <string name="brevent_service_command_copied">Command copied: %s</string>
    <string name="brevent_service_adb_running">(Enabled)</string>
    <string name="brevent_service_usb_connected">(USB connected)</string>
    <string name="brevent_service_run_as_root">Run as ROOT</string>
    <string name="brevent_service_success">Brevent service started successfully. Please click app icons to choose them, and brevent them</string>

    <string name="fragment_apps_user">User Apps</string>
    <string name="fragment_apps_system">System Apps</string>
    <string name="fragment_apps_framework">Framework Apps</string>

    <string name="process_retrieving">Retrieving processes status, just a moment. . .</string>
    <string name="process_retrieving_apps">Retrieving apps, just a moment. . .</string>

    <string name="process_status_running">Running</string>
    <string name="process_status_standby">Standby</string>
    <string name="process_status_stopped">Stopped</string>
    <string name="process_not_running">(not running)</string>
